Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Hang in there. I'll save you soon.
Just a bit more. I can go home now.
James!
Yi-rang, run!
Yi-rang!
One second.
It seems Team Lead Lee Seong-min
was the inside man.
Really? Okay.
Who was that call from?
It's my wife.
SEOUL FIRE DEPARTMENT
She's showing sensitivity to light
due to aftereffects from the incident.
Our biggest concern is whether
her dissociative disorder will persist.
We'll have to monitor her
through ongoing psychotherapy.
Yi-rang, I'm sorry.
I arrived too late.
Everything's going to be okay.
Yun Yi-rang, the daughter of Rine's CEO
whose kidnapping gripped the nation,
was dramatically rescued after five days.
Shockingly, it turned out
that the suspect who died at the scene
was the leader
of the girl's bodyguard team.
Fortunately, Yi-rang did not receive
any major injuries and is resting.
The police believe this kidnapping
may have been committed by a group
and plan to hold additional investigations
for possible accomplices.
Congressman Park Gyu-taek!
-Step down right now!
-Step down!
MARCH 2020
He's going in. Get ready.
Wake up, Park Gyu-taek!
-Wake up!
Real estate speculation and lease fraud!
Park Gyu-taek!
Step down!
-Step down!
I'm a three-term congressman.
How could you bring me here?
My apologies, sir.
This is a core district,
so for the next election…
Let's just say a few words
as greetings and end it.
Yes, sir.
Also, tell the host
not to ask me any questions.
Yes, sir. I'll make sure.
CONFISCATE ALL PROFITS!
You bastard! Die!
Hey! Cover him!
For Christ's sake.
You couldn't even stop that.
You can't do anything right!
Geez, it stinks.
How disgusting. Get out of my sight!
Disgusting?
God, I'm so sick of this.
Who do you think
caused this mess in the first place?
What did you just say, you punk?
Are you out of your mind?
Gosh, did you hear that?
I thought your ears were clogged up,
but I guess not.
If you had such good hearing,
how come you can't listen to the people?
Has this punk seriously lost his mind?
Hey, fire this punk. Now!
What a damn lunatic.
Who says you can fire me?
I'm quitting first.
Got it?
What are you…
I'm quitting.
Geez, you stink.
You reek like rotten trash.
Let's never meet again.
You disgusting jerk.
Sir.
That lunatic!
Who am I?
Where am I?
What am I doing with my damn life?
Geez.
Damn it.
Geez!
Nothing ever works out, damn it.
You're still living like this?
God, I'm going to lose my mind today.
Who are you
and why are you speaking informally to me?
I'm disappointed, James.
You got the wrong person.
I'm not James. I'm Seo In…
I'm not James. I'm Seo In-jae.
If you say Seo In-jae backwards,
it's Jae-in Seo.
It sounds like James.
Yun Yi-rang?
Long time no see, mister.
Yi-rang!
Let's pretend we hugged.
Seeing how prickly you are,
you really are Yi-rang.
Hey, mister.
Let's work together.
What? What are you talking about?
Find this person for me.
But we just met after 20 years
and suddenly this?
Who is…
Oh, this man.
I have something to report.
Yes, the man who left
with the three-billion-won reward money,
Myung Jin-su.
Right. I remember.
The CEO… I mean, your father.
He even had dinner with your father.
Anyway, why are you looking for him?
You know I hate to lose.
What are you saying? I don't understand--
A game called abduction
staged by the culprit who fled.
Who do you think was the winner back then?
Wait, are you saying…
EPISODE 7
LAW FIRM INVICTUS
"Invictus"?
Okay, the operation will begin.
REPORT
So after your husband died,
you're in conflict with his ex-wife's son
over the inheritance?
Yes.
The cause of death was a heart attack.
It was a chronic disease.
A cloning disease?
Like cloning? Is that a real disease?
A chronic disease.
It means he suffered for a long time.
Oh, of course!
That's right.
And his ex-wife's son suspects
you're connected to your husband's death?
Right?
Isn't that ridiculous?
Look at this.
He was 88.
He was going to die on his own.
Why would I bother to create a situation
to make everyone suspect me?
I may be stupid, but I know that much.
I've seen it on TV.
Coincidentally, it happened two days
after you registered your marriage.
Attorney Bae.
You don't think...
I killed my husband too, do you?
Ma'am.
Whether you killed your husband or not,
that is none of my concern.
What the hell are you saying?
I'm saying
my role is to just help you, my client,
receive a lot of inheritance.
I misunderstood. So that's what you meant!
Oh, honey. I mean, Attorney Bae.
You're amazing! Absolutely awesome.
Also,
this is the will my husband wrote
before he died.
Could you take a look at it?
Do you think
I'll be able to get all of his fortune?
Well, the issue is
your husband was on medication
for dementia.
Why would that be a problem?
If there's a record of dementia
at the time the will was written,
his son will likely file a suit
to have it nullified.
Then, the will
won't likely hold any power.
Damn it.
So I won't get anything?
This is ridiculous!
Calm down, ma'am.
I think
I can come up with a different plan
that's safer than this.
What do you mean by something safer?
We'll first frame the son
as a bad son or a big scoundrel…
But my stepson isn't that bad.
Right.
We'll take advantage of the forced share
and include the inheritance
he passed to his son before his death.
Then, we'll demand the loss
of the son's forced share.
If we demand at least 1.5 to 1--
At least 1.5 to 1. I like that.
Attorney Bae, you're amazing.
You're so smart, honey.
Let's go with 1.5 to 1.
Anyway, I feel relieved thanks to you.
I'll come up with a good strategy
to make his son give up the lawsuit.
I have such good luck.
I'm so happy to have met you.
Okay, but if you could let go…
It's because I'm so happy.
-Right.
-I'm so glad I met you!
Mom!
Son.
Son?
What are you doing here?
Mom.
Dad just died,
and you're already with another man?
In broad daylight?
Mom, how could you do this?
Son, this is not what you think it is.
Don't you lie to me!
I saw it with my own eyes!
Sir, you're very mistaken…
I mean, this is a misunderstanding.
Oh my!
So you've been having a fling
with my stepmom?
Since when? Tell me!
What are you talking about?
Please let go.
-Let's talk it--
-Yeah, let him go and let's talk!
Was it your idea to seduce my dad,
register the marriage,
and write the will?
What?
Are you the one controlling my stepmom?
What? Why would I do that?
Hey, you dirtbag!
Son! How dare you act so rudely
in front of your mother?
Let go of him now!
Did you just take this bastard's side?
What is wrong with you?
Son, do you still not know my type?
I don't like old men
with side parts like this!
I like K-pop idols!
Son!
Son! Hey, someone call an ambulance!
Don't just stand there and watch!
Call an ambulance!
Son!
Geez, I said no pictures.
Hey, kid. Stop them, will you?
Hey.
Stop them, you idiots.
-Sir.
-Yes?
Did you collect all the samples here?
Yes, we're almost done.
-Sir.
-Yeah?
Goodness, you're the famous lawyer
Bae Young-min. I'm a big fan.
Hello.
How did you end up creating this mess?
What?
No, it wasn't me.
He grabbed me by the collar first.
Whether he grabbed you by the collar
or you grabbed him,
that's not what matters, man.
The victim is on the verge
of death right now.
What are you talking about?
-Hey. You didn't report this yet, right?
-No, sir.
Geez.
My goodness.
So, should I report it, sir?
Gosh, I am your fan, but…
Look, how about this?
Before this gets any worse,
how about you settle with the victim…
Settle?
You don't want to?
-Or we can talk about it at the station.
-Yeah, that's safer.
Wait, hold on.
I think just settling would be better.
-You're going to settle?
-Yes.
Okay.
I mean, we already have
the car ready though.
-No, wait…
-Well,
this is why you shouldn't exploit
innocent people.
All the profit from this operation
will go to the produce store owner.
I can't believe he framed
a victim of a fire for arson
and pocketed the legal fees.
Call him in about two hours
and wrap it up, James.
This is the hottest case right now.
I can already smell the stench.
MYSTIQUE CEO
COMPENSATION FOR DAMAGES
I think we have our next load of laundry.
Your Honor,
as you can see
in the submitted medical record,
the defendant Lee Hye-yun's skin problems
were caused by her irregular lifestyle
and sick building syndrome,
and her preexisting case
of eczema recurred.
Experts unanimously agree this has
no connection to Mystique's cosmetics.
Despite this, the defendant produced
and distributed a malicious video,
claiming that all these symptoms
were caused by Mystique's products.
By filing a lawsuit, she inflicted
significant damage to the company.
Mom, I don't see Bae Young-min,
the guy you had a fling with.
Rumors spread
about his affair with a client
and attempted murder charges.
He won't be able to show his face
for a while.
WITNESS
Ms. Lee Ye-sol, you recently met
with Lee Hye-yun, correct?
Yes.
We met and shared a meal once.
What did the defendant say when you met?
She told me to keep my mouth shut.
But it had been a while…
Gil Beauty produced a fake witness again?
It's because of what happened
five years ago.
Back then,
she suggested we commit fraud.
What?
She showed me the pimples on her face
and said she came up
with an awesome, life-changing idea.
Then, she handed me a new Mystique product
that was popular at the time.
Hey.
I liked it, so I bought that for you
with my own money.
I didn't suggest anything.
Don't be ridiculous.
Defendant, please remain silent.
Calm down.
Please continue.
What did she say to try and persuade you?
She said I'd at least
get enough for a building.
Hey!
When did I ever say that?
Do you have proof?
Yes, we do have evidence.
Ms. Lee Ye-sol,
you may return to your seat.
We submit as evidence the messages
Lee Hye-yun shared with the witness.
Here are the deleted messages
recovered from the defendant's phone
through forensic analysis.
Could you display them, please?
TEXT MESSAGE ANALYSIS REPORT
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU, SO BE QUIET
IT'LL BE OVER SOON
WE'LL EACH AT LEAST GET A BUILDING!
No… That wasn't me.
Seriously, I didn't send those messages!
We will now deliver the verdict.
For repeated production and distribution
of videos falsely accusing Mystique
on your personal Neotube channel
to receive large amounts of compensation,
and for greatly impacting
the company's reputation and sales,
the defendant, Lee Hye-yun,
is sentenced to one year
and six months in prison
and three years of probation.
Prison?
You think I don't know
this is all a setup?
How much were you bribed for this?
Defendant, please be quiet.
You will be dismissed
for insulting the court.
I was the one who was insulted.
Why won't you even listen to me?
Don't touch me.
I'm going to sue all of you!
Don't you see? I endured all this…
Gil Beauty, no matter how much
you fabricate the evidence with money,
you can never fool me.
I'll head to Gil Beauty's car.
James and Gu-ho, proceed as we planned.
Let's do this.
She's coming out!
Can you tell us how you feel
after winning this lengthy lawsuit?
Thanks to everyone
who supported Mystique…
I was able to endure
thanks to all of their support.
We at Mystique will devote ourselves
to doing things the right way.
We will make an effort
to become an honest
and healthy company that fulfills
its social responsibility.
Thank you.
WASH & HAPPY
Okay. She's coming.
OWLY MOTORS NUMBER 1 MAINTENANCE
Ma'am, are you okay?
Oh no.
-Ma'am, the tire--
-Wait!
Let me check.
Gosh.
Gosh, this…
Did you make enemies or something?
My goodness.
This is…
This was stuck deep inside.
What should we do, ma'am?
Well, what else?
You should call your insurance.
My store doesn't deal with
luxury tires like these.
Gosh, these tires are nice. My goodness.
That discharger
is a super close range type.
You have to get very close.
Hello, is this the insurance company?
More. Get closer to her.
Get right up close.
What's this? Hang on.
Yes, our license plate number is…
-Yes.
-Your hair…
-Hold on.
-Our car's…
You lose a lot of hair
when the seasons change.
-Hello?
-Gosh, so much hair.
-How dreadful.
Hello?
What the…
All right.
What a chill guy.
Wait, why is this…
It turned off?
My phone's out of battery, ma'am.
Oh no.
Your phone died? What will you do now?
Here.
What are you--
So pretty…
Stupid mosquito!
I missed it.
A mosquito in the middle of winter?
Gosh.
Geez.
-Global warming is getting really serious.
-It's dead.
My goodness.
What?
Yours is dead too.
Well, shall we go in first?
You can make a call inside.
Let's get inside for now, ma'am.
I'll serve you our signature coffee.
Come on.
Yes, Seonbi-ro 1104.
-Yes, we got a flat tire.
-Here.
This is Owly Motors' signature coffee.
The old-fashioned way.
I'll help you charge your phone.
Yes, please hurry.
If you just plug it in,
all the data in Gil Beauty's phone
will be transferred to this server.
Okay, bye.
Secretary Choi?
This actually worked out.
It had been hectic.
No, it hasn't been hectic.
It's okay.
I'm okay too.
-It's okay…
-It's…
It's okay.
She's strong.
They will be here as soon as possible.
It's okay.
Forget about Gil Beauty's phone
and secure her secretary's.
This is great.
What a chill guy.
Just as expected?
No, better than that.
She didn't seem like that at all though.
You act stupid
whenever you see someone pretty.
When did I ever act stupid?
He wasn't acting stupid. He was dazed.
To be honest, I was kind of shocked.
Who would think she's James' age?
-Is that how it is?
-Sorry.
Okay. Fine.
-That's not what I meant.
-Okay.
Who cares if you were stupid or dazed?
All those tears she shed
in front of court.
Those were...
crocodile tears.
They weren't tears one sheds
when they're sad or happy.
They were like a lubricant that comes out
when a predator chews its prey.
Anyway,
they were fake tears.
Gil Beauty is
a Goguryeo Women's University graduate.
She became a celebrity
through a local beauty contest.
As she gained attention
starring in commercials,
she suddenly retired.
She launched the cosmetics brand Mystique
and expanded her business
at an intimidating pace.
As the founder of a company with nearly
500 billion won in annual sales,
she's a monumental figure
in the beauty industry.
Ms. Gil has arrived.
Ms. Gil is here!
Ms. Gil!
Hello, ma'am.
This way.
BODY SCAN RESULT
Ten percent body fat.
I won't accept
anything more than twice that.
All employees must keep
their body fat percentage in the twenties.
Your appearance is also your talent.
Gil Beauty,
known as the "Korean goddess of beauty,"
is beloved by the public
for her calm, intellectual image
and immaculate personal life.
However, the venom in her sharp tongue
is beyond your imagination.
The things she says to her employees
are mostly insulting criticisms.
To Gil Beauty,
beauty is the truth and justice.
What am I looking at right now?
You are the faces of Mystique.
Competence is a must,
and managing weight is essential.
Didn't I say that?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You need to answer my question properly.
I asked, "Didn't I say that?"
And "I'm sorry" isn't an answer to that.
Well…
You told me to lose weight.
A timid attitude like that
won't help you in life.
I will rectify it, ma'am.
Get on.
Sorry?
But people are looking.
That's embarrassing,
but not this?
I drank too much water earlier…
I was going to start on a diet today.
BODY SCAN RESULT
Your body fat percentage. It's 32.57?
What a pig.
From now on,
make it 15 percent!
What did I say?
Fifteen percent!
You pigs.
What? Pigs?
This lady is too harsh.
She's ruthless.
Gil Beauty is the queen of power trips
and the queen of lawsuits.
When you hear this, you'll get the idea.
Would you like to hear
about the slander lawsuit
or the compensation
for mental anguish one first, ma'am?
Is that compensation suit
from the one who quit last time?
Yes, from the aesthetics department.
File a countersuit for a false accusation.
Twenty-three employees have quit.
Three lawsuits are currently in progress.
Even if I lose the lawsuit,
the psychotherapy,
all different types of barbiturates,
and the horrible rumors
will ruin their lives.
Insomnia caused by their anger
will torture them forever.
They won't be able to get
a decent job either.
So isn't it obvious
they'll either go crazy or go broke?
Well, it's even better if it's both.
Gosh, she's terrible.
She spent all that money
to stomp on the powerless.
Getting revenge is so easy.
With just a few pennies,
you can completely ruin a person's life.
We received apologies from those we sued
for leaving malicious comments.
What should we do about them?
Stick to the original plan.
But there were a lot of comments
that were too mild to deserve punishment.
So, except for those people…
Secretary Choi.
I heard well-trained dogs don't bite.
-Ma'am?
-What if we go easy on such comments
and create negative opinions
about Mystique?
Are you going to take
responsibility for that?
Ma'am,
I should've known better.
You have to be stricter on comments,
especially at an important time like this.
My apologies, ma'am.
Wait.
First, pigs. And now, dogs?
Sit.
Okay.
Does she think
people are dogs and pigs or what?
Put it down.
Eat.
Good boy.
Am I a dog?
That's how Gil Beauty controls people.
Today's trial went exactly
according to Gil Beauty's script as well.
Her script?
Are you saying the Neotuber
who made that fuss in court
was a victim and not a perpetrator?
She is the true victim
of the halo effect and the horn effect.
Five years ago, Gil Beauty collaborated
with a few famous influencers
to promote her new skin care products.
Gudi, Gudi! Hi, subscribers!
It's the girl
who tries the makeup for you.
I'm cosmetics girl Lee Hye-yun!
Hi!
Everyone, I just got a facial
with Mystique's new line of products.
Did I pay out of my own pocket?
Well, not this time.
Mystique reached out
and proposed a collaboration.
Isn't it crazy? You can tell, right?
I can't believe how my face is glowing.
No wonder people praise Mystique.
That influencer was thrilled
to collaborate with Mystique.
But her dream moment didn't last long.
It was the start of her long suffering.
My skin broke out,
so I'm wearing sunglasses today.
I hope you understand…
It's because of
Mystique's new line of products?
I doubt it.
That doubt ruined her life.
Her face soon became
covered with blemishes.
She already had sensitive skin,
and it became so flaky
she could no longer livestream.
Gosh, that's really bad.
So, Lee Hye-yun filed a lawsuit
against Mystique.
But Gil Beauty switched idroxenon,
which can cause skin problems,
to the eco-friendly
skin-whitening ingredient, sobinyu.
Then, she erased all traces of idroxenon,
as if it had been never used.
So basically, she switched
bad ingredients with good ones
and manipulated her cosmetic products.
Is that even possible?
You're seeing it right now.
As you know,
our country's still conservative.
So, an influencer with pink hair
and provocative clothes
wouldn't have been seen in a good light.
That gave the halo effect to Gil Beauty,
the successful businesswoman
who was beautiful to boot.
Lee Hye-yun, who seemingly made money
the easy way with her pretty face,
got the horn effect.
The halo effect and the horn effect.
During the five-year lawsuit,
Lee Hye-yun tried to change
people's impressions of her…
She looks so cheap!
-She's so desperate.
-She makes me want to puke.
Go kill yourself.
It was too late to change
the already negative impression of her.
Lee Hye-yun ended up looking
like a money-grubbing streamer.
And Gil Beauty was praised
as the goddess of beauty
fighting against injustice.
And yesterday,
Gil Beauty submitted evidence
definitive enough to end the trial.
Wait, but if they did
a forensic analysis on the phone,
it means that conversation was real.
In the era of AI,
evidence can easily be fabricated.
MANIPULATED EVIDENCE RECORDING
In the era of AI,
evidence can easily be fabricated.
This must end here and now.
Ahead of this key contract,
I won't accept even the slightest flaw.
Find someone
who's in urgent need of money.
ONE MONTH AGO
Seriously,
Mystique's going to pay for this.
How's the trial going?
Will you be okay
facing a major corporation?
I'll have to do everything I can.
Isn't that Lee Hye-yun?
The influencer suing Mystique?
I heard her skin completely broke out.
I need to use the restroom.
It'll be over soon,
so keep your mouth shut.
Hye-yun, don't you think
you should stop now?
I'll give you a nice cut, so be quiet.
It'll be enough
to at least buy a building.
DELETE
Gil Beauty hired an influencer
who was a friend of Lee Hye-yun
to fabricate the messages
and manipulate the forensic data.
Well done.
Thank you.
Now that we've confirmed it,
let's move on to the next step.
Why are you looking at me?
Is there something on my face?
You have a plan?
What?
Sit.
I'm sure Yi-rang does.
We need to know why Gil Beauty
had to manipulate the evidence
and rush to finish this lawsuit.
But how?
"One-day experience with Mystique
for invited beauty content creators."
We only have a few days left.
SSONY SYNDROME, RISABAEK, OFFICE WORKER G,
HYO-JIN CHO, LAMUTE, MASK GIRL
My gosh, I was already imagining it.
Gu-ho does have a pretty face.
Do I look good today?
Yes, very pretty.
Thanks.
ONE-DAY EXPERIENCE WITH MYSTIQUE
FOR INVITED BEAUTY CONTENT CREATORS
Hello.
We're honored to have here
beauty creators currently at the forefront
of the cosmetics industry.
I heard Mask Girl was coming too.
She's hot these days.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Sorry, I'm late.
I'm Mask Girl.
Are you sure about taking off your mask?
Of course.
Mystique's skin care
is the best in the industry.
I had to take it off anyway.
Besides, it would be so rude
to keep the mask on
in front of so many famous influencers.
I have a cold.
I'm so glad I came.
I can't believe I'm meeting Mask Girl.
You're so pretty.
Thank you.
Could you please stop drooling, Gu-ho?
That's not something I can control.
Anyway, are you sure
nothing's going to happen?
Don't worry.
I already contacted the real Mask Girl
and said that the event was postponed.
Get it together.
Don't get dazed again
and forget what to do.
When did I ever forget…
All right, we will soon begin
our first program.
Shall we dig into
Mystique's secrets together?
-Yes!
This is great.
If you've all changed,
we'll begin the yoga program.
Follow me.
This way, please.
Yes, this way.
Mask Girl! It's this way.
Okay. I'm coming.
Please come in.
Let's go. Are you not feeling well?
No.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
This way. Quickly.
It's starting soon.
In the Downward Dog Pose,
raise your right leg toward the ceiling.
Then, bring your knee close to your chest.
Go to a lunge between your hands.
Raise both hands in the air.
How do you do this?
Watch your voice.
Keep your tone high.
Like this?
A woman's beauty
starts with a healthy body.
Yes, you're all doing well.
What's going on? Was he caught?
Ignore the feeling!
What feeling?
You don't want to know.
Tighten your stomach.
And all at once, up.
Yes.
Good job.
Everyone, don't let that fluster you.
Bend forward slowly and Uttanasana.
How long are you planning to do that for?
What am I supposed…
What am I supposed to do?
There are security guards everywhere,
and the staff follow me everywhere I go.
Should we take it to the next level?
That's enough to kill him.
Next, you'll try the Mediterranean diet.
Let's keep going forward.
Wait. Let me use the restroom.
Kim Sam-sik!
Excuse me. What's going on?
That crazy woman… I mean, man…
I mean, patient escaped from our asylum.
We ask for your cooperation.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Darling?
Darling, no!
What the…
Geez, what the…
Men in black!
Be quiet!
Geez.
What on earth?
I really had no idea
it was this hard to live as a woman.
You were all dazed and happy
with those beautiful women.
And now, you're complaining?
It's really tiring. I'm serious.
It's a shame.
What is?
What's a shame?
You weren't planning
to use that for real, were you?
How about a light dab?
No. Hey…
Look, it's on!
What's wrong with all these participants?
Don't you know it's important
to cast ordinary people for this program?
We'll keep searching
and send you a new list.
Since this is the first live show
after the lawsuit,
I told you numerous times
to put extra care into this!
Yes, ma'am.
Next.
Are these the new samples?
Yes, ma'am.
But this is too much of a replica.
Adding one herb to the original product
and disguising it with a new package
is not always going to work.
The collaboration with Charpentier.
An investment of 300 billion won
in facilities!
The contract will only happen
if they approve the samples we send.
Don't you know that?
We've been pulling all-nighters
and doing our best to--
What's the point of pulling all-nighters?
The results are awful!
They're garbage!
Get out.
Go.
You too.
Yes, ma'am.
She's expecting
a major contract with Charpentier?
She had a reason
to end the lawsuit in a hurry.
Charpentier sounds familiar.
The top European cosmetics company
whose moisturizer costs 500,000 won.
One bottle of moisturizer
costs 500,000 won? That's ridiculous.
Wait, Yi-rang got an idea. Right?
Yi-rang's got an idea.
What does Mystique mean?
Mysterious.
Secretive.
That's why it's more attractive.
Right.
We'll lure in Gil Beauty in a way
that is mysterious, secretive,
and thus more attractive.
The more she wriggles,
the deeper she'll sink
into the quicksand of ambition.
Once she falls in, she can never get out.
THE OPERATION BEGINS
Could you please read this?
I'm looking for my father.
Please take a look.
Could you please look at this?
Could you…
Please take a look at this.
MYSTIQUE BASIC SKIN CARE SAMPLES
I'm looking for my father.
Could you please read this?
Thank you.
Wait.
Okay, they fell for it.
Yes?
No.
This isn't it.
Find someone who will look gorgeous
when we give her a makeover.
Someone who looks unstylish
but has nice skin.
And someone thin,
so she'd look good when we dress her up.
Yes, ma'am. I'll send more people
to the train station.
Don't say you work at Mystique
for the time being.
Sorry? What do you mean, ma'am?
Look at your damn skin.
Take care of it, will you?
I didn't have time for it.
What a sorry excuse.
I just got a photo from the train station.
How about this woman?
Today, we're going to transform
Ms. Y from Gangwon Province.
There.
It'll feel cold.
First, clean your skin
with a toner from Mystique.
Okay.
Her skin is very nice.
What do you think?
Our skin care products are enough
to make your skin moist and glow.
This is what I meant
when I said Mystique's strength
is in sticking to the basics.
Now, I will begin applying the makeup.
Let me turn you first.
Here are the products I used today,
from skin care to makeup.
How did Mystique's Green Line of products
change Ms. Y from Gangwon Province?
I can't wait to see.
Shall we meet her now?
Please come out.
My goodness.
As they say,
"A woman's transformation isn't a crime."
This is just perfect.
How does it feel to have makeup on?
I've spent all my life in the countryside,
so I've never tried makeup on.
I guess that's why I feel
a little bewildered.
I think I look pretty.
This is a perfect makeover.
An unimaginable upgrade.
With Mystique, it's possible.
Why don't you try the makeup you saw today
to return to your twenties
and your most beautiful days?
Just like our guest today.
Do you not like your makeup?
No, I love it.
I'd like to have this every day.
Maybe I shouldn't remove it.
It kind of doesn't match
what I'm wearing right now.
Secretary Choi.
Yes, ma'am?
Bring the gifts from each Mystique line
and all the outfits she tried on.
Yes, ma'am.
Gosh, no!
The appearance fee is enough for me.
She probably doesn't go
to a dermatologist.
But her skin is so nice.
Gosh, my face feels a bit dry.
Which skin care products do you use?
It's nothing special.
I just use anything I can get my hands on.
-Here you are.
-Right. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Here you are.
"Beautifying Toner."
Beautifying Toner?
Ms. Gil.
Good job yesterday.
Thank you, ma'am.
You should've gone
to a dermatologist sooner.
Well, I had to clean up,
so I didn't have a chance to go yesterday.
But yesterday, Choi Eun-seol…
Good night, Ms. Oh.
Good work, everyone.
Eun-seol.
Could you tell me
your bank account number?
-Sure.
-Here.
That must be pretty bothersome.
Right. Yes.
Thank you.
One second.
This will help a bit.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Her skin improved just overnight?
Is that possible?
I've never smelled
anything like this before.
Nice texture.
And it's easily absorbed.
What is this?
Which skin care products do you use?
It's nothing special.
I just use anything I can get my hands on.
Could this be…
the secret to that girl's skin?
Secretary Choi!
Yes, ma'am.
That woman…
No, check the ingredients in this.
Yes, ma'am. I understand.
This product is definitely
not sold on the market.
I also checked for its patent,
but it wasn't registered either.
That means it's handmade.
Are you sure
what I'm seeing right now is true?
Yes, ma'am.
There are no chemical ingredients at all.
With natural sparkling water as its base,
it's full of minerals
that are good for the skin.
And the natural preservatives
from these wild mountain herbs
reduce skin irritation.
Team Manager Oh's pimples
disappeared overnight after applying this.
It was probably
due to the spadeleaf extract.
What you'll like about it
is the added magnolia oil that gives it
a luxurious, long-lasting aroma.
I think I also smell something else.
And the possibility of using it
to collaborate with Charpentier?
Compared to all the products
we developed and sent to Charpentier,
it excels in terms of ingredients.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then, what's the phone number
of that girl from yesterday?
I already checked,
but she didn't leave a number.
And all we know about her address is
"Manbaeksan Mountain, Gangwon Province."
But can we find her with that?
I'll send someone
to the train station first.
Manbaeksan Mountain.
Manbaeksan Mountain. Beautifying Toner.
BEAUTIFYING TONER
What?
MANBAEKSAN BEAUTIFYING TONER
KOREA! JOURNEY TO FIND A LEGEND!
What the heck? It's so tacky.
GOODNESS! A VILLAGE OF ANGELS
AT MANBAEKSAN MOUNTAIN?
"A village of angels?"
Where on earth is it? Damn it.
Oh my gosh.
Have you heard of
Manbaeksan Mountain Beautifying Toner?
My nephew probably knows.
Eun-seol.
What? How come everyone here
has such nice skin?
Is this all Beautifying Toner?
I knew it.
Make it exactly the same as this.
Copying it wasn't enough,
and she's going to steal the patent too?
That wasn't part of the plan.
-No!